<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Love is the Way to All</title>
    <link>www.loveway.one/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Love is the Way to All</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:07:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="www.loveway.one/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:06:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Change Your Mind, Change Your Life All of us have the power to transform our lives into anything we can imagine. As divine, creative beings we have the rare gift of self-directed evolution. Our talent for it is so powerful that we do it instinctively, so long as the right conditions exist. What we think, we increase. When we get caught in situations that trap our thoughts, however, we can’t grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise: Creating Space</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_creatingspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:06:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_creatingspace/</guid>
      <description>In order to draw the light closer to us we need to make some room for it. Let’s take a peak at what that will look like. We’ll do this exercise once now, at the beginning, and once again at the end, after we’ve had a chance to dive into some of the core components.
I’m going to have to speak figuratively a lot here, because English lacks the language to explain certain things with any reasonable amount of accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Fields</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/mindfields/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:06:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/mindfields/</guid>
      <description>Mind Programs and Mind Viruses Thought forms are patterns of cognition. Programs are thought forms that are so rooted in memory and habit that they begin to express themselves unconsciously. Many programs have a life of their own, due to something about their nature that recombines your thoughts in order to replicate and spread to others. Memes are to mind as genes are to body. Some of these memetic programs are good, and some are maladaptive, serving their own interest first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Names and Stories</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:06:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/stories/</guid>
      <description>Metaphorical Vision Let’s all agree to disagree about certain ideas and phrasing that I’m using here. Whatever traditions you’re working with, I think we can all agree that there’s something powerful happening within our minds and our bodies that we can’t describe using words. Our people are awakening and evolving so rapidly that no ancient tradition can hold all the answers. There’s wisdom in teachings everywhere, but what’s given to you by other people will only get you so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auras</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/auras/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:07:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/auras/</guid>
      <description>Sensory Interpretation is a Learned Behavior Every brain can process information from the mind field, but each person has a preference for how that information gets translated into sensory awareness. Some brains will interpret vibratory signals as high-pitched sounds or deep, low tones. Some will see flashes of light, colored orbs, or closed-eye images. Some will even smell subtle odors that can’t be explained by the substances around them. Most people, however, are primarily kinesthetic integrators, meaning they detect energies as if with a sense of touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise: Sense the Local Aura</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_auras/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:07:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_auras/</guid>
      <description>Lay back and relax. Close your eyes and breathe for a moment, allowing your body to ground and become more present. Now, without opening your eyes, raise your hands towards each other and hold them about a foot apart. Focus on the sensations of your hands. Try to feel each finger clearly, the nails, the muscles, and particularly the skin. Bring your focus to your hands, as if you’re getting ready to move them but holding back just shy of motion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assemblage Points</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/assemblagepoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:07:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/assemblagepoint/</guid>
      <description>The Anchor in Multidimensional Space Everyone has an assemblage point, a place where energy flows freely between the physical and energy bodies. Carlos Castaneda coined this term in his book The Power of Silence and described it as a heart-center that anchors a person within the spiritual dimensions. He claimed that everyone’s assemblage point traveled slightly, but “sorcerers” (source-rers) could move theirs at will.
The position of the assemblage point relative to the body is the dominant influence upon a person’s mental and spiritual experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise: Move Your Assemblage Point</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_assemblagepoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:07:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_assemblagepoint/</guid>
      <description>Take a moment to sense where your focus is oriented. Do you feel a lot of energy in your head? Legs? Hands? Do you feel grounded, like you’re “in your body”, or do you feel light and airy, like you’re floating off in space? Take a moment to gauge your emotions. Do you feel peaceful or a little anxious, like there’s something you need to do? Are you feeling highly stimulated or somewhat drowsy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Higher Dimensions</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/higherdimensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:07:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/higherdimensions/</guid>
      <description>Non-Local Space The distance between two mind fields directly affects the strength of their interactions, but that distance is not measured exclusively in 3D space. While it is difficult to perceive higher dimensions clearly and even harder to explain them to others, here is a story that helped me to understand.
Cultures around the world have known for a long time that there are three aspects to reality: the physical, where our bodies exist, the mental, where our minds join together and push apart, and the spiritual, where all things come together as one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Field Interactions</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/mindfielddynamics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:47:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/mindfielddynamics/</guid>
      <description>The Unique Enfolding of Polarity Differentiates Mind Fields If the world of down is infinitely diverse and the world of up is infinitely unified, then how do the two ever meet? We humans clearly have mental experiences that differ from one another, yet are similar in many fundamental ways. This is because mind is not localized, but infinite in concept. The spectrum of consciousness spans the two dimensions of up and down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise: Breathing the Field</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_breathe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:08:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_breathe/</guid>
      <description>Part A: Closing the Field  Beginning in a calm, grounded state, bring your focus to the surface of your skin. Start with the skin on your hands, then expand your awareness to include all the skin all over your body. Try to feel it all at once, to get a gestalt or summary impression of its sensation. Increase your focus by imagining tiny vibrations in your skin, like a shiver that’s too fast and too faint to perceive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessing Infinity</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/accessinginfinity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:08:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/accessinginfinity/</guid>
      <description>Bouncing Between Known Assemblage Points Hopefully by this point your energy will have shifted noticeably a few times. Hopefully you’ve gained an inkling of what its like for your assemblage point to move to different locations in the up/down matrix. The location of your point is about more than just how you feel, it’s a question of what matters are close to your heart, of what you desire, and what now weighs upon your mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise: Making Requests of Mind</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_expandmind/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:09:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/exercise_expandmind/</guid>
      <description>Expand the Local Field to Invite Information from the Realm of Infinite Concept  Open your field and let excess energy drain away into the environment. Ground yourself by imagining your feet plunged deep into cold dirt, rooted in the earth. Allow all your thoughts and emotions to seep away until you feel calm. Close your field back up by imagining a shell forming at the edges of your aura.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conclusion</title>
      <link>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/conclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 21:09:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.loveway.one/solsticetalk/conclusion/</guid>
      <description>Summary Now you have a story, ideas I’ve given you about the nature of mind. It arises like cymatics from resonance patterns in the electromagnetic field. It makes impressions on awareness that may create memories. These memories become addresses that we can return to by shifting the assemblage point, a combination of awareness and intention. By learning to listen to our bodies, we can invent a language to communicate with our subtle senses in order to detect and direct mind field energy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>